<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="settings_cat_cycle">Startup / Smoke Mode Cycle Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_info_one">During Startup and Smoke modes, the cycle time (Auger On Time + Auger Off Time) is fixed, and does not change dynamically based on any other inputs. Effectively, this may allow you to adjust the rough smoke temperature depending other external factors like ambient temperature (seasonal), etc.</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_info_two"> If a PMode of greater than zero is selected, the PMode is multiplied by 10s will be added to the Auger Off Time. [For example: Cycle Time = Auger On Time + Auger Off Time + (Pmode * 10)] This calculation is reflected in the table below. If you don\'t want to use PMode to configure the cycle time, then select a PMode of 0.</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_note">P-Mode is used for both Startup and Smoke modes, but not Hold mode. For more information about the P-Mode click here</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_mode">P-Mode</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_table">P-Mode Table</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_summary">Click here for a P-Mode chart</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_auger_on">Auger On Time</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode_auger_off">Auger Off Time</string>
    <string name="settings_pmode">Mode %1$s</string>

    <string name="settings_cat_splus">Smoke Plus Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_enabled">Smoke Plus Enabled by Default</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_note">Smoke Plus Mode can be toggled on/off by tapping the smoke plus button on the dashboard. The button will be highlighted indicating that smoke plus is enabled. Smoke Plus will cycle the fan on and off during smoke and hold mode to promote additional smoke generation. Fan cycling will only occur between the above min/max temperatures.</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_min">Min Operational Temp</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_max">Max Operational Temp</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_on_time">Fan On Time</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_off_time">Fan Off Time</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_fan_ramp">Fan Ramping Enabled</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_ramp_dc">Fan Ramp Duty Cycle</string>
    <string name="settings_splus_fan_ramp_note">Fan Ramping will ramp the fan from off to the desired duty cycle instead of just turning on to full speed during Smoke Plus cycling. You can control the ramp duration by setting the Fan ON Time below. The desired duty cycle can also be set below.</string>

    <string name="settings_cat_cntrlr_config">Controller Configuration (HOLD Mode)</string>
    <string name="settings_cat_cntrlr_pid">Controller Configuration</string>
    <string name="settings_cntrlr_title">Selected Controller Type</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_title">Controller Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_summary">Setup PID and Cycle settings</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_pb_note">This is the temperature band centered around the set point, that the controller is active. If the error is less than PB/2, the command is 1.0. Higher PB\'s decrease controller response to error. [Default=60.0]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_pb">Proportional Band(PB)</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_td_note">Time (in seconds) to predict the future value. Higher Td makes the controller more responsive to the Error Rate of Change. [Default=45.0]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_td">Derivative Time (Td)</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_ti_note">Time (in seconds) to eliminate the integral error. Higher Ti makes the controller less responsive to accumulated error over time. [Default=180.0]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_ti">Integral Time (Ti)</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_sw_note">Window +/- from Set Point for triggering Overshoot condition. When in Overshoot, Output is set to min. [Default=12]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_sw">Stable Window (Degrees)</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_center">Center Ratio</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_center_note_standard">Center of Cycle Ratio, which is specific to the way this PID will behave. Higher Centers increase system response at high set points. Lower Centers increase system stability at low set points but may keep the system from reaching high set points. [Default=0.5]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_center_factor">Center Factor</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_center_note_auto">Center Factor multiplied by Set Point. Higher Center Factors increase system response at high set points. Lower Center Factors increase system stability at low set points but may keep the system from reaching high set points. Controller accounts for F to C conversion. EX: At 240F(115C) center is 240 * 0.0012 = 0.288. [Default=0.0010]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_tau_note">Time constant for the Smith Predictor. This is the time it takes the system to reach 2/3 of it\'s final value after a Set Point change. Higher Tau decreases system sensitivity to model mismatch. [Default=115]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_tau">Tau</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_theta_note">Time delay in the system. Theta is measured after commanding a Set Point change as the time it takes from the initial command to seeing initial temperature rise. Higher Theta makes the system more sensitive to delays in the system. [Default=65]</string>
    <string name="settings_pid_cntrlr_theta">Theta</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_no_config">No configuration options are exposed for this controller</string>

    <string name="settings_cat_cntrlr_cycle">Controller Cycle Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_cycle">Cycle Time</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_cycle_note">Amount of seconds for a complete cycle. At the beginning of each cycle, the controller will check the current temperature and set point to determine the cycle ratio (auger ON time / auger OFF time). [Default=25]</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_u_min">Min Cycle Ratio</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_u_min_note">Minimum percentage of cycle where the auger is on. This is to prevent flame–out which can happen with a cycle ratio of less than 0.1. (0.0 – 0.99) [Default=0.1]</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_u_max">Max Cycle Ratio</string>
    <string name="settings_cycle_cntrlr_u_max_note">Maximum percentage of cycle where the auger is on. This is to minimize possible overshoots, or overcompensation in temperature. (0.0 – 1.0) [Default=0.9]</string>

    <string name="settings_cat_lid_detection">Lid Detection</string>
    <string name="settings_lid_open_enabled">Lid Open Detection</string>
    <string name="settings_lid_open_thresh">Open Threshold</string>
    <string name="settings_lid_open_pause">Open Pause Time</string>
    <string name="settings_lid_open_note">If enabled, the system will attempt to determine if the lid was opened and temporarily suspend the PID. If the temperature drops below the threshold (percentage of the hold temperature), a lid open event is triggered. Once lid open is detected, it will pause the PID for the specified amount of seconds.</string>

    <string name="settings_cat_keep_warm">Keep Warm Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_keep_warm_s_plus">Smoke Plus During \'Keep Warm\'</string>
    <string name="settings_keep_warm_temp">Keep Warm Temp</string>
    <string name="settings_keep_warm_note">The Keep Warm mode is a specified Hold temperature, that you can define, that can be activated by a timer or notification targets. When the grill is active, you can click on the timer dialog and check the Keep Warm box. Or you can click on the Notification Targets for any of the probes and select the Keep Warm box. The Keep Warm function will be activated when a probe notify target has been achieved or the timer has expired. The Grill will exit the currently running mode and switch to Hold Mode then attempt to maintain the temperature set above.</string>
</resources>